[{"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "3"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "4"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "2"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "4"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "2"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/长今.svg", "num": "3"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "3"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "4"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "1"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "4"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "1"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/长今.svg", "num": "3"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [1], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "2"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "4"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/长今.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "1"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "4"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/长今.svg", "num": "1"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "2"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/小莉.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "2"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "1"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/长今.svg", "num": "3"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/长今.svg", "num": "1"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "2"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "3"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [2], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/多多.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/辰辰.svg", "num": "1"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "多图单选框(带容器）", "stem": "3个盘子原来有同样多的草莓，3个小朋友各吃了一些，都剩下一些，谁吃的最多？", "content": [{"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/球球.svg", "num": "4"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/月月.svg", "num": "3"}, {"src": "v2/通用/人物/人物_front/天天.svg", "num": "2"}], "type": "select-img-1"}], "answers": [3], "knowledges": ["比多少"], "resource": "", "type": "选择", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-2-08"}]